<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Cesar Hernandez</title>
    <link>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Cesar Hernandez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 18:06:26 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//blog.ceshm.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Structure from motion</title>
      <link>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 18:06:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/structure/</guid>
      <description>This might be a misleading title as this is not about the computer vision term, but a nice way of reminding myself that going for a walk, changing scenery, talking to different people, and having new experiences are crucial for having a healthy life.
We all have bad days were we feel really uninspired. Sometimes it really surprises me how bad it can get. Getting stuck is the best way to call it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conoce tu pueblo</title>
      <link>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/pueblo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2020 18:07:35 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/pueblo/</guid>
      <description>Hoy mi tía nos estaba contando sobre varias personas de Playa que han sido víctimas del crimen organizado. Que si Fulanito tenia un negocio y le empezó a ir bien y tenia dinero y se compro una camioneta y la estaba presumiendo, y entonces le cayeron los malos y le empezaron a pedir el derecho de suelo&amp;hellip; Todas estas personas con negocios pequeños son las más vulnerables. Los de abajo siempre lo han sido.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaporwave is the perfect art movement for a post COVID-19 world</title>
      <link>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/vaporwave/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2020 17:42:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/vaporwave/</guid>
      <description>Several weeks into quarantine and it&amp;rsquo;s easy to see how many aspects of our life have changed for good. This pandemic has left a deep mark on all of us. Our interactions with others have been forced to go online, we&amp;rsquo;ve learned how capable we are to get work done remotely, and also how much we still need to improve and build. It&amp;rsquo;s clearer than ever how important this virtual mediums are and the pain points we still need to overcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maker&#39;s block</title>
      <link>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/makersblock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Apr 2020 18:07:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/makersblock/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I wrote my first post. I also have been struggling to work on my projects, but a lot has happened in the last months. First of all, the current pandemic that is forcing most of us to stay home, which even for a hermit like me has had a negative impact on my mental health (those daily walks and trips to the café were an integral part of my routine).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropping out of college</title>
      <link>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/dropout/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 18:06:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//blog.ceshm.com/posts/dropout/</guid>
      <description>I started waking up everyday feeling miserable, most of the classes seemed pointless and I felt like I just didn&amp;rsquo;t belong to that place. This is how I spent my last two years attending college. It was really hard to realize what I had to do, but now I feel like dropping out was one of the best decisions I could have made.
In 2012 I started studying the B.S. of Software Engineering, a degree that is relatively new but has started to be offered by some universities around Mexico in the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
